<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
	<ID>EXAMPLE_PLANET</ID>
	<!-- The ID of the planet this xml file is for -->

	<Entry>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Name>Procedural Projection</Name>
		<Curiosity>1</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>
		<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>2</ID>
			<Text>The Nomai built a simulation accessible through a projection pool.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>3</ID>
			<Text>During the first practical test, three Nomai became trapped inside the projection. To find the exit, they went to the middlepoint between the three Anchors.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>4</ID>
			<Text>A Nomai named Melina was bothered by the predictable nature of the projection, noting that knowing everything of an enviroment contradicts the Nomai's curiosity.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>5</ID>
			<Text>A Nomai named Calad was bothered by the lack of nature within the projection. Another Nomai noted that knowing the nature was simulated would defeat the purpose of adding it.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>6</ID>
			<Text>A Nomai named Primm was bothered by the artificiality of the projection, noting it seemed like "an attempt by someone to recreate their structures without understanding why they were built."</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>7</ID>
			<Text>The projection is procedurally generated from the knowledge of whoever is inside it.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>8</ID>
			<Text>I found a Stranger-styled area above the Nomai structures.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>9</ID>
			<Text>I found a projection stone that allows me to return.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>10</ID>
			<Text>The Nomai concluded they wouldn't finish this project, as they considered it to go against Nomai philosophy.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>
